Who took Riley Brennan?
Shelby Oaks is a horror, mystery film directed by Chris Stuckmann.
A woman's obsessive search for her missing sister leads her into a
terrifying mystery at the hands of an unknown evil.
Mia, played by Camille Sullivan.
Robert, played by Brendan Sexton III.
Morton Jacobson, played by Keith David.
Riley, played by Sarah Durn.
Tarion, played by Derek Mears.
Janet, played by Emily Bennett.
Shelby Oaks is a 2025 American supernatural horror mystery film produced, written, and directed by Chris
Stuckmann in his feature directorial debut, with Mike Flanagan as an executive producer.
It stars Camille Sullivan, Brendan Sexton III, Keith David, Sarah Durn, Derek Mears,
Emily Bennett, Charlie Talbert, Robin Bartlett, and Michael Beach.
It follows a woman (Sullivan) determined to find her sister (Durn), who went missing
while investigating the mysterious abandoned town of Shelby Oaks.
The story for Shelby Oaks was written by Stuckmann
and his wife, Samantha Elizabeth.
An independent production, the film was crowdfunded through Kickstarter.
By March 2022, it had become the most-funded horror film
on the platform after raising $650,000.
Principal photography took place in Stuckmann's home state of Ohio in mid-2022.
Shelby Oaks had its world premiere at the 28th Fantasia International Film Festival on July 20, 2024, after
which Flanagan became attached to the project, eventually becoming an executive producer.
The film was subsequently re-edited and underwent reshoots before it
was released at Fantastic Fest in September 2025.
The film was released theatrically in the United States by Neon on October 24, 2025, to
mixed reviews from critics and grossed $6 million at the box office.
The film explores themes of rape, grave, ohio, woods, paranormal.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.